Well, I came over here to
the YouTube because they were hating on
me on the Instagrams. So,
good to see y'all. Happy two Fri-
Friday? Friday?
Happy Friday. Um
and
uh
Hold on.
I ain't going to lie to you, Rolando. I
was like, "Let me just go over to
YouTube and say hi to Rolando."
Hey, Richuals.
I got to see Richla in person
again.
That was twice this year, y'all. Twice
this year.
Um hold on.
Okay.
So,
um
No, Lakisha is a brown. That's what I
was talking about over on Instagram.
Like, this country is just simply not
interested in the truth. Like, it really
just Like, the truth is just not
salacious enough, which is weird. Also,
can we point out that people are like,
"Oh, it's going to go down when these
files come out." And I'm like, "How?"
How's it going to go down?
Who Who Who's doing the going downing?
The people in the files?
Are the people
who would be doing the going downing?
They own the prisons.
These are all the people in charge.
Like, this would be guillotine time.
But, that's not going to happen.
You know how many You know how much shit
really should be like on fire right now?
Like,
there's a lot of shit that should not be
left standing right now that is
definitely standing.
Just saying. So,
if you think
like, these people are going to go down,
negro, please.
Oh my god, stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
Stop.
Stop. What the hell is this?
Um
Y'all talking about jail. The What?
Jail?
Make me Explain it to me.
Explain Okay, I want y'all to explain to
me
how
these people in these files are going to
end up in jail.
And I want you to then explain to me
what you know about jail.
That's why they You know, they got spots
they can go to. Argentina, Israel.
Pedophiles be going to Israel and living
their best life. And they're not even
like important. They're just regular
pedophiles.
Thank you, Yuneil Ortiz.
Reese, why you on? You should be asleep.
It's like
9 10 11 12 1 2. It's 2:00 a.m. in the
morning. Almost 3:00.
Celine
I mean, listen.
Celine, you said it, not me.
Cuz I'm I'm I'm like, what what are we
Jail?
The bitch is in jail right now with her
dog.
Oh, that's right. Y'all don't have
daylight savings. So, it's 1:47 for
y'all.
What?
Why are you doing this?
Ah!
Stop.
Why are you printing like this?
Ah!
Where's my
There we go.
Okay.
So,
we are also in the midst of
this fake Venezuela war,
which is nuts,
by the way.
Like legit nuts.
And
I can't even
like we're seeing this in real time, and
this is Iraq all over again,
in real time.
What are y'all thoughts?
Ooh, the history of the CIA, I need to
watch that.
It's going to piss me off, but I need to
watch it.
This week in the UK, we had Remembrance
Day to commemorate fallen soldiers of
World War II and World War II, World War
I and World War II, and all wars
included, which is when everyone wears
poppies, but I just feel so deflated in
that. You should, because all of that is
nonsense.
You can see people's addresses and
names.
I mean, I don't know
why you would care
about these people's addresses and
names, but
um
I feel like if you doing that, you you
looking real you like really doing some
espionage, cuz you can
I don't know how you're seeing people's
It's reversed.
It's like
I mean, you can see that it's a label,
but I don't know that you can actually
see persons like people's names.
Karen said, "They lying."
I would love to go outside the US, too.
In due time.
Raspberry
beret.
You've been thinking seeing you live on
the book tour and whatnot, spreading the
good gospel.
My one semblance of relief is at least
now I know the news is just lies. I
don't feel guilty about not being able
to keep up with said lies. I hear that,
cuz honestly, when I see people like
reading through the Epstein files, I I
thought about it and I was just like,
yeah, I don't I don't have an interest
in doing that. I don't need to read
through the files.
I I really don't know that that's going
to do me any good. What what what is
You know, like
like they have like databases. Like
they've indexed databases, you know, cuz
that's what AI can do. So, I saw like
the the Tao and the courier, they had
like indexed the the the emails,
so that you can literally go in there
and see how many times certain names
were mentioned. Which is what which you
know, for what it's worth,
certain names, Democrats,
and
um
One second.
Hold on, y'all. I'm multi multi-tasking.
Exactly, Isabel.
Like that's why I'm looking at people
talking about like the the Republicans,
the Democrats. I'm like, the Democrats
been had access to these.
My glasses?
My glasses are Jimmy Choo, and I got
them at Costco.
So, I'm shipping out your Malcolm
bonus Here's the Malcolm bonus bundle.
It's the Malcolm pin,
and it comes with the big ass sticker,
and the sticker sheets,
and
that's a magnet.
Um
I don't want to do like
holiday cards, but I want to do cards.
And I've been trying to kind of think of
like
people can vote,
and then the the ones they vote on are
the ones like the top three will be the
ones that I make.
Something like that.
How does that sound?
Here's the thing. I know that it's a
holiday time, and we don't want to do
Christmas,
but I still think it's nice to
send correspondence.
You feel me?
This is the Malcolm poster.
So, I feel like, you know,
I feel like in regards to that,
I want to make I want to
create in that regard. Does that make
sense?
Excuse me.
Uh
Grey Dove. Grey Dove, you better say
that. Grey Dove took the words right out
my mouth. We need to get into the habit
of sending mail anyway. These electronic
pathways may not be like they are for
much longer. I am in 100% agreeance with
y'all.
Now, something This is kind of a
prototype. It's not going to be this
big. It's not going to be this style,
but something I'm working on is this.
So,
I've been working on the prototype for
it. Uh this isn't going to work, this
version that I did.
But,
I am
uh
I'm still creating.
So,
we're going to keep fiddling around with
it.
See
what transpires.
Card you found in a second hand store.
So, okay. So, in regards to the
correspondence stuff,
how does that sound to y'all?
The options on there are Nat Turner,
Sista Soldier, Fred Hampton, June
Jordan, Assata Shakur, Malcolm X,
Kathleen Cleaver, and Mumia Abu Jamal
Jamal.
Usually, if it's a metal
grommet punch used for the spinner. So,
I was trying to find that,
and
I was not successful. So, I guess I have
to keep looking for a metal grommet
punch for the spinner.
metal
grommet
for spinner.
Yeah, like I can see all the grommets,
but
but I don't see
how to do the spinner.
Isabelle,
I think that's the most fascinating
part. I don't know why it's fascinating
to me. It makes sense, but like
me and y'all Steel Squad, we have the
same sense of humor.
I'm not going to bed until I ship all of
these, 61 of these. So, I just want
y'all to know that.
Oh, it's an Eddie Murphy film?
I've never even known I didn't even know
there was a Eddie um Murphy film.
Okay, so correspondence.
Okay.
So then, I'm going to I'm going to come
up with some ideas cuz I had come up
with something the other day that Fatima
had said she liked.
Um
I wrote it down,
but
Malcolm wrapping paper.
But then, it's like counterintuitive.
Because if I if I'm giving wrapping
paper, that assumes that we're getting
gifts,
and we're not.
I'll send you wrapping paper wrapping
I'll send you Malcolm wrapping paper in
February.
We need to change what we celebrate.
Thank you, Chacy. We need to change what
we celebrate.
Like we should be giving gifts like on
Black August, we should be like sending
gifts to
like folks that are imprisoned
that we consider to be like American
prisoners of war.
You know, like that's what
like to me like that's the way that we
celebrate Black August. Like
um
we should have like on James Baldwin's
birthday, we should
give each like you should always give
each other a James Baldwin book or
something. Like we should I I Maybe I'm
going to create a a calendar of new
holiday.
A calendar of new holidays.
This type of shit I'm on.
Cuz I'm just like we're we're
celebrating the wrong things.
You know, we're celebrating the wrong
things. And we're celebrating things
that don't in a way that doesn't help
us.
Like on James Baldwin's birthday,
it's like you go to dinner with your
friends, or you have dinner with your
friends, but everyone comes prepared
with a James Baldwin passage that
they're going to read, and y'all are
going to discuss.
An ancestors calendar would be nice.
So, Rolando, what you're suggesting is a
calendar,
but like with I with like holidays I've
made up?
First of all, we should have an altar
all year round.
And so,
there'll be people on the calendar who
um they'll have like a symbol by them
that means like light a candle that day.
Like on You know what I mean? And
Damn, y'all stay giving me work.
You what's wild, though? I know exactly
how I would get it made.
And I can do this very quickly.
I can do this very quickly.
Well, there you have it.
Okay.
I'm on it like that kryptonite. Straight
straight on that kryptonite. I be on it,
man. I be on it all day. Straight up.
Straight if you want me, you can find me
in the
Yeah.
>> Rolonda said sorry and thank you.
Uh in the hey hey Atlanta had a time for
a time, y'all.
Okay.
Y'all wasn't of age. Some of y'all in
here wasn't of age during the Atlanta
era, but baby it was a
time.
I will never forget hosting the MTV 2 2
Dollar Bill concert from for Lil Jon in
um Atlanta and
they did the whole show, but then they
was like, "Let's do a encore. Let's do a
encore." And they did
lovers and friends.
Oh my god.
Tell me again
that we'll be lovers and friends.
Bum bum bum bum tell me again
Uh
baby
how you doing? You got it fine, but I
know that you got in mind that I'm
cuz I'm feeling like you're the seeker.
I can't leave you alone. Take a shot of
this and see Take a shot of this strong.
It's going to be on. The house ain't got
way too crowded. I'm about to end up
calling it a night.
You should hunt your girl so you shaking
see.
Pull up BB got gun, a shotgun, a GT with
me. She said,
ready to ride.
Yeah, as long as you get inside, you
can't change your mind. Now that's the
line where you're like, "Whoa whoa
whoa."
Sounding a little rapey.
When she does get inside, she absolutely
can change her mind.
Uh she is well within her right to
change her mind when she gets inside.
And uh that there is
That is the result of somebody who's
like,
"I don't want to get sued by a groupie."
That's what that is.
Don't mean to sound impatient, but you
got to promise, baby. He's literally
like, "Listen,
let's not do this thing where you come
to my house and you just want to drink
wine. Are you trying to smash?"
Are you trying to smash?
Cuz I'm not trying to play Uno.
Okay?
Celine put asterisk lawyer footnote.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah.
Please tell your lovers and friends that
Usher, Jon, and Ludacris had to do it
again. Hey!
Please tell y'all I'm telling y'all it
was a time.
Like it it's so not a time in that way
now that like I can't even believe that
we got to have that time.
Listen, Isabel.
I'm not saying it can't happen. He's
just saying it's not happening.
That's all he's saying.
He's saying we're not That's not what
we're doing tonight.
We not about to leave here and you hit
me with a Uno reverse, literally. We not
about to do it.
I've been knowing you for a long time.
That same man
is now
a Muslim.
Yes, brother Lil Jon.
As-salamu alaykum.
Crunk and B. I'm telling y'all he it's
That was when I was DJing, too. I was in
the club.
We was just Oh my god. And then knock if
you buckle come on.
It was just a It was just a crazy time.
From the window
to the wall.
Then it what that pop pop pop. It was to
me it was the last time that like
everybody was dancing.
Cuz nobody dances in the club now. They
literally just stand there. I mean I've
seen videos cuz of course I'm not in the
club.
Can you imagine me in the club? What the
hell would I be doing in the club?
That's really what it is. Nobody had no
phones.
I remember I had to pick up something
from my homeboy in the club and I pulled
up in spandex and a big shirt. And
people in the club was like, "Damn, you
you on your own flavor."
Cuz everybody was dressed up and I
really was like, "Sir, sir, yeah, I'm
coming here to pick this up from Jon."
That was a time. I'm so I feel so
fortunate that I got to live during that
time.
Because
baby, I twentied my 20s.
Okay?
I twentied my 20s.
I'm also like I'm glad that I'm not
putting out my memoir the way that I was
going to put it out before because I
feel like I didn't like I feel like
I feel like I left out like I twentied
my 20s.
I felt You know what I mean? Like I felt
I I I I really twentied my 20s
and I feel like I didn't really get to
to like do really put that in a book in
the way that I want to.
My 20s in hip hop. Like I didn't even
really I didn't really get to do that.
Cuz
man.
I I want to do I just want to do a whole
chap I just want to do a release called
Your Favorite Rapper Is a Lame.
And the whole book is just short stories
of interactions with cornball ass
rappers. And I don't say nobody name.
I don't say nobody name.
But
that's the whole book.
That's the whole book.
The whole book.
It's just
And then with each chapter, I talk about
the lesson I learned.
I got to get more packages. Hold on.
Please tell your lovers and friends
that Usher, Jon, and Ludacris had to do
it again.
I mean, I'm like really in my revolution
bag now, so I can't just like
do a tell-all.
But there's some stories I want to get
off.
There's some stories I really want to
get off.
I also have a character called Harlem
Hightower
and I thought about like telling the
story of my like New York experience
like
through her. And it'd be the life and
times of Harlem Hightower.
Oh, somebody was in here trying to judge
Rolando.
Unless I was Rolando check somebody. We
don't do that.
Hey
Isabel!
>> Oh my gosh, I want to know.
I want to know. That just took me back
to a time when I went to dinner with
uh this producer Q-Tip Phifer
Ja Rule the Damager
and Pharoahe Monch.
I used to be having some random ass New
York nights.
Terry dude.
Someone was judging.
What's there to judge? I'm 44. You
judging me in my 20s?
No.
The 20s is a time for
figuring your life out and
you know
making errors
learning the hard way
things like that. That's what your 20s
are for.
It's not I'm not saying that you
Like there's this shit you just you know
you're not your brain isn't even fully
developed.
Yes, Rolando.
And then 40s
is putting it all together.
And being like oh.
Daphne, welcome.
Daphne just said
Yeah, same Isabelle.
Same.
I mean I was never I was I was always
I was emotionally
Would we say emotionally intelligent and
emotionally mature are the same thing?
Right, they're different.
I was emotionally intelligent,
but I wasn't emotionally mature.
Right, Lena M. I agree. Yeah.
Because I feel like Someone said that's
autistic-tastic of you.
Yeah, like I could process the emotions,
but it was like ah like now what? And
like nobody around me taught me anything
about men. Zero, zip, z-
like zilch.
So
you know I didn't know who was the
actual emotionally immature one.
Like it took
a lot of
bumps and bruises
to
really like
understand
what I was also like
regurgitating
and
versus like what I actually felt.
Cuz I think that's also like the big
one. Like you're not even realizing like
you this ain't even how you rock. You
just doing this cuz this is how you came
up.
Or this is
you know the only example you've seen
type shit.
Same same.
Nola Bebida, same same.
Help me find my way. Nobody want to go
and do that love, huh?
Y'all don't understand Q-Tip was my like
really really really good friend.
And then he just flipped.
People get funny when you about to move.
He just um
he flip moded.
We were super tight.
And then we went to go see Dave
Chappelle one night.
And he
like I was talking to Dave and he was
like yo we yo let's go.
And I was like hold on a second and then
he like came up and was like
when I say let's go
it's time to go.
Trayshawn.
Then we got in the elevator and I was
like who the fuck are you talking to, B?
Who the fuck are you talking to?
And
um
and we were leaving to go to like dinner
with Leonardo DiCaprio or something.
And
uh
he was we were in the elevator. He was
like nah you you acting like a groupie
and it was time to go.
And I was like and we literally we when
we walked out of the building at 30 Rock
or where were we at? At Radio City?
Like he went this way
to the car
and then I literally went and just got
on the train and I didn't say nothing.
And then I got up top to Harlem
and he sent me a text and was like
where'd you go? And I was like nah you
was being really disrespectful. And he
was like you got to know when to talk to
people after a show and um you know you
you was doing too much. Which is an
insane thing to say to me because by
this point I'm Amanda Seales. Like I'm
not some like little girl trying to
figure life out. Like
and
um
he was not trying to be in a
relationship with me. No.
So he was jealous, but I don't know why
and I to this day
to this day
I have no idea
why he
um
flip like that.
Jealousy. What made you buy the same
shoes as me?
Jealousy.
>> What did Terry do? I missed it. Hold on.
Okay.
Q-Tip avoided Amanda's mom for dear life
at a venue one night.
Yeah, he did. It was really weird.
It was really weird.
Like ran.
You know, I know some people would say
like, "Oh, Amanda's being messy." But I
don't feel the need to keep the secrets
of nonsense.
Particularly if people who
like dropped me.
Oh my gosh, Jedi.
Come here.
No, you can go there. You can go there.
That's your spot.
No.
No, you can go here.
Good girl.
I will never understand this, Rachel.
Just children.
But I will say that the people I know
that like popped off in their early 20s,
like you know, they got money, they got
fame, they really arrested.
They never, you know, they never really
matured.
Who was the best rapper I ever
interviewed?
Like who gave the best interview?
Um
DMX.
Who did I always look forward to
interviewing?
Hm.
You know what's interesting? I'm sitting
here and I'm like
2 Chainz when he was a part of
um Inner Circle was a really good
interview. Tity Boi.
Um
That's a great question. I really have
to think about it because
to be quite honest, no one like comes
immediately to mind
as like
"Oh, I really liked interviewing this
person."
Cuz I knew Whereas like in this era of
my life, like I can tell you very
specifically like I love interviewing
Eugene Perrier cuz I'm always going to
learn something, right? Like
um
I
Like I love when me and Mark do some
type of interview cuz I know we just
going to be laughing the whole time.
I never interviewed Gangstarr. I've I've
interviewed
Have I ever interviewed Dante?
I've actually never interviewed Mos Def.
I just know him.
Um
I've only did like a short interview
with J. Cole.
We He was on this like live thing I was
doing for VH1 and I interviewed I I did
like live interviews with all of the
people on the show.
So, that's the only time I've
interviewed J. Cole.
But he was very nice.
Very sweet guy.
Um
But I can't say
that I can think of anybody off top
that I'm like, "Oh, I really like I
really liked interviewing them."
Who is the newscaster Zeteo?
Oh, Sam Cracker Sam Which one?
Sam Cracker or
um
or Meddi?
So, I interviewed Kendrick like before
he was popping at all. Like I got
Kendrick on this like MTV show I was
doing back in 2012
called Hip Hop POV. And I was like,
"Y'all need to get this cat Kendrick on
here. Like you need to get Kendrick on
here." And I had met Dave Free and
Kendrick because I had went to a
Kendrick show like at like
some little spot in Brooklyn
and I was cool with them. And Dave Free
switched up when Kendrick popped off.
But back in the day, they you know
um
like I wanted to use All Right as the
intro music for my special I Be Knowin.
And um the executive producer Jesse
Collins reached out
to Dave Free cuz he knew him and asked
if we could use the first 30 seconds of
All Right.
And he said he needed to see the special
before he would give me
um clearance to use 30 seconds of All
Right in as as the as the coming out
music for my intro special for my HBO
comedy special.
I said,
"Let me take another route."
So,
I called Charlamagne and he put me in
touch with um
the owner of TDE.
And he was like,
"Yeah.
We're fans."
And then I texted Pharrell
and he was like, "Yeah.
Just use this text as proof
and send it to the um to the EPs or to
standards."
And so, that's how I got
All Right
as the
uh intro music to my HBO comedy special.
Sometimes you just got to go over folks'
head.
>> Yes, Mom is correct.
Aim for top management. So, I hit up Top
Dog
of Top Dog Entertainment.
What would I say to my 20 self now?
These niggers don't matter.
That's what I would say.
Focus on yourself. These niggers don't
matter.
I spent so much time
trying to get these like trying to
matter to these niggers.
I spent so much time trying to matter to
them, y'all.
Oh my god, so much time.
And they didn't matter. None of them.
So, that's what I would tell her.
Really, Lindsey.
Love that we got you in the know.
Oh, yay. Thank you, Suzy.
Yeah, Terry. Single is where it's at.
Single is where it's at.
I can't
I just can't stomach
the
um
To be quite honest, I don't even find
myself in the company of men at this
point.
I'm like in the company of my homies
or
like my animals or myself.
So,
it's like, you know, what how am I going
to meet somebody? I'm not. And that's
fine.
Yes, and we have talked about this
before. Never again cohabitation.
Like I have a person that
um
like we
we will always be like we we love each
other. Like we'll always be in love with
each other. Like
I mean, he's with somebody.
And that's fine. Like he
like he's with her and
it's actually like it's good for him to
be with her.
We also know what it is.
So,
no, forever. I don't want to marry
nobody and I don't want to live with
nobody.
I've did it. I've done it. It's fine.
Is it in a four sunrise or four sunset?
Like we dated like we have like a whole
story, but then we've become like
legit friends. And even though
like we we've always had that romantic
element, like this time in this time in
this part of our timeline, like we're
just
we're friends. And like we don't talk
all the time.
But whenever we do talk, like we're very
honest, you know? Like he'll tell me
about his lady.
He'll ask me advice.
I always give him honest advice.
Um
when I was with Davon, same.
And
you know, I it's been really cool just
to see him develop as a man.
Like as an actual like man and a person.
Um
it's been really cool to see.
And I feel like in 10 years
you know,
that's that may be the right time for
us.
According to him, hey man, we like hey
man, we lifers, don't trip.
Hey man, we lifers, don't trip.
No, he's saying before sunrise or four
sunset because that's a reference to the
Julie Delpy film with Ethan Hawke, the
series.
Yes, it we're still before midnight.
We're still before midnight.
Um
I don't keep all of my exes in my life,
but
in some cases some of my exes it's not
like we weren't
it's not like it didn't work because we
were they were bad people.
You know?
It just didn't work.
So,
I mean, I DJed an ex's wedding.
But I can tell you that like
even if me and homeboy never got
together, like I know love and I know
what it is to be loved and I know what
it is to be liked.
Cuz that's the one.
That's the one.
I know what it is to be liked, to have
that whole situation all together. And
that's not common. And and I I can tell
you I've been in many a relationship
where I was not liked.
I was admired sometimes.
I was
envied.
I was possessed.
But I wasn't liked.
How have I worked through relationship
trauma to come to where you are now? I
had to
really do my own
like identifying of what my role is.
And work on healing that.
But
one thing about Reese is he going to
tell you about some movies and some TV.
Okay.
I need to have Reese come on and do uh
watch don't watch.
Cuz Desmond be busy. I need to have
Reese come on from England from London
and tell us what to watch don't watch.
Okay.
Cuz Reese be getting us together.
High
taste.
You can't teach taste, y'all. You can't
teach taste.
So, Burns Ray, I can live and love
long-term.
I can like and love long-term.
That's not the problem.
But if you're not honest with me and
you're not consistent with me, I'm not
going to fuck with you.
I respect you. I may love you still. I
have a very good friend who I will love
forever. But he not going to keep
playing with me.
You know? I've lived in New York now for
a year and he has not come see me.
You not going to keep playing with me.
And telling me, "Oh my gosh, this has
been so crazy."
It has it? Go fuck yourself.
Love you.
Yes, Rolando.
That crazy has it.
That's it, Dana Cooper.
Lola gag 'em.
That's it.
Go fuck yourself. Love you.
You know, me and my good friend
I expressed to her
something that I that I felt that, you
know, hurt my feelings
the other day.
And she was like, "Damn.
You ain't never tell a lie. That was
whack of me."
And
you know, I've had to do the same
with her.
Where I've had to be like,
"So, I fucked up.
My fault."
That could be one of my correspondence
cards.
Go fuck yourself. Love you.
You really on some bullshit.
I love you, but you really been on some
bullshit.
Just dropping you a line.
To keep atonement top of mind.
How did I sing I told y'all niggers?
That was my That was my Kamala theme
song.
I told y'all niggers.
Shit, I told y'all niggers.
I did, though.
I did.
Ooh, a best of Miss Ceal's quotes
postcards.
Hmm.
Just like I told y'all niggers, they are
about to get rid of Donald Trump.
I'm trying to tell you.
I'm trying
to tell you.
Honestly, Reese, I can't even front.
Every year
I've started doing this thing where
I um
I put a row of posted notes of my goals.
And
I hit them.
Y'all, I don't hit almost all my goals.
I'm only missing one goal.
And that's a That's a ancestors
uh coloring book.
A What Would the Ancestors Say coloring
book.
But my other goals on there were to sell
my were to pedal my wares, which you see
me doing right now. Um I also
my other goals was
um
to
Hold on. Why is this
My other goals was
to um
to do the live stream of What Would the
Ancestors Say.
Uh I also had on there to
Originally, I had on there to publish
um
to publish what's it called
my memoir, but then we took that off,
and so I replaced it with publishing
What Would the Ancestors Say.
So,
You know I can't forget about the kids,
Gabriel. I can't forget about the kids.
So, yeah. I feel I feel good about my
goals. How about you, Reese?
How do y'all feel about your year?
I said I told y'all
niggers.
Rachel, I kind of think that, too.
Cool. Cool. Cool.
I mean, listen. I became a whole other
person this year
than I've been for the last 10 years.
And that was a big deal for me because I
realized like, "Damn, I've been living
the same life for like a really long
time." Other people had kids, they got
married, etc., etc. Like, and my shit
just been kind of the same. So, I'm
really like glad that I was able to
switch things up and step into a
different space. And I'm still stepping
into that space.
So,
you know, sometimes the transition is
really it.
That's right.
Lola, go get 'em.
The key to addiction is figuring out
why you're an addict.
What is the
What is the thing?
That's That's That's a hard path.
What is the thing? And then you got to
face the thing.
And then you got to figure out what are
the other things that be looking like
the thing.
But first you got to get out from under.
All of y'all who are addicts on here,
I'm praying for you.
I'm hoping that your ancestors are
giving you
more than strength. I'm hoping they're
giving you clarity.
You know?
I'm hoping they're giving you clarity.
Trayshawn, I can tell you
lack
has been one of the most
uh fruitful times of my life.
What's that, Reese?
All of us looking at here waiting for
Reese to say,
"Oh, you know we all thought he was
saying there's some type of part two of
Interstellar, right? Was it just me?"
Cuz that's what I definitely thought he
was saying.
There's an interstellar object meteorite
heading towards Earth for December. I
hope it's aliens.
Come on down.
I'm so sorry, Trayshawn.
I'm so sorry.
Credit scores are such absolute
bullshit.
This is me, y'all.
Listen, Terry D, I'm pretty sure that
I'm an alien.
So, I think maybe that's why me and
these earth men don't be jiving.
Cuz it's like we not
we're not even of the same biological
situation, though.
I'm about to start rewatching by
Battlestar Galactica.
So, I can get really back into the mind
of the Cylons. Pretty sure I'm a Cylon.
Pretty sure.
I told y'all,
niggers.
Is the art in my new book drawn by me?
It sure is. It says on the front of the
book, "Illustrations by Amanda Seales."
Well, Brandon, I'm currently taking an
astrology class. I'm behind, but I'm
about to catch back up.
And then, maybe I can try my hand
looking at your chart.
Pisces man,
uh.
But, I mean, I don't know what your
risings are. So, let me not completely
judge you. But, on the surface,
Pisces man is just
annoyance.
I'mma tell you, my ex was a Pisces man,
and he said to me,
"I'm a loner, but I still want to be
missed."
It's like
what?
I still want you to miss me.
I do want you to be obsessed. I ain't
going to lie to you. I do want somebody
to be obsessed with me, because I'm
going to be obsessed with them.
That's the thing, though. It's not a
one-sided thing. I'mma be obsessed with
you.
So, be obsessed with me.
Yeah, Gemini burger cancer. Cancer
sounds crazy.
Life is dynamic. That's funny.
I told y'all,
niggers.
All right.
See, this is what I love about y'all. I
could just shut up, and y'all would
still just
chat away.
By the way,
Jedi's here asleep.
Thank you, Michael.
May the force be with you.
There's a hot springs in Grenada.
I River Sallee.
And you go, and then they give you like
a whole
um mud
like
they like slather it all over you. It's
this one woman, she be over there just
auntie-ing you with mud.
Hi, my sugar plums.
Hi.
What are you thinking about?
Jedi is literally making air biscuits.
Grisela.
Yeah.
I did date drug dealers till 39. I can't
even can't even front.
Can't even front.
Oh my god, Jedi. Jedi, please, please,
please. Please.
Oh god.
Okay.
Um
I think Rachel asked me how the cats
are. They're so good.
They're really good. It's like It's like
they've been here all the time.
Have I ever taken back cheaters? No.
I've never had anybody I've never caught
anybody cheating on me. I'm
sure they did,
but I never caught anybody.
So, there was never a like where I had
there was there was never a situation
where it came to a head and I had to
decide
if I was going to stay with it or not.
You think I should date Wale?
Fuck Wale.
Gross.
You mean the same Wale who tried to
fight me?
Like physically fight me on stage?
And my boyfriend at the
time had to come and snatch him up by
his neck?
And he was like, "This would never
happen in in in DC."
And Hussein was like, "Nigga, we ain't
in DC."
The fuck?
We in Philly.
Then Karen Civil Then he went on the
internet. Right after that, he went on
the internet talk about Amanda Seales is
irrelevant. I want y'all to know, this
is like
This is
2012.
Amanda Seales is irrelevant. We are in
2025.
And me and y'all are still here. That
nigga was trying to write me off in
2012. Amanda Seales is irrelevant. Mind
you, I was hosting the the Roots Picnic.
I was hosting the actual picnic. So, how
the fuck am I irrelevant?
No, Orlando passed away.
So,
yeah, fuck Wale and everybody who fucks
with Wale.
Then Karen Civil tried to broker a
you know, an opportunity for us to to
meet and to
you know,
reconcile.
I was down.
Mind you, I'm the victim. Right? He's
the one that attacked me. I was down.
And then he last minute
decided that he didn't want to.
He got in my face because he didn't like
that I had tweeted
um
cuz he was performing and I tweeted,
"This nigga Wale just moonwalked on
stage.
I never imagined
that women would be throwing panties
on the stage for him.
But he be rapping though.
Also, like why would you in this day and
age of 20
25, the year of the old gods and the
new,
suggest that I date a rapper?
Good night, Polly. See maker.
Healthnista, my Chicago book signing was
a dream.
Truly.
It was a dream. I
was at a place called Birth into Books
in South Side Chicago. So, we was in the
hood, y'all.
We was in that
hood, baby.
And
it was just like a really cozy space,
but even before we started the beginning
even though before we started the book
talk,
um
the owner of the store
Jalima, her mom cooked me a home-cooked
dinner and we literally sat at a dining
table
and ate dinner together.
And I hadn't had a home-cooked meal
where like we sit together and eat in I
can't even tell you how long.
So,
that was just really
it was really like welcoming and
beautiful.
I will be in DC on December 2nd and I'll
be in Baltimore on December 3rd. So,
mark your calendars, all right? Yes, I
am cool with Adrienne. I will always be
cool with Adrienne. Adrienne Adrienne
Bailon, she's just a She's the kind of
person where like if you're not cool
with Adrienne, something's wrong with
you.
Cuz she's just not a funny style person.
She's just a very stand-up gal.
I haven't talked to Adrienne in over a
year. If I call Adrienne tomorrow,
she'll be like, "Oh my god, what's going
on?"
Uh possibly, Sita. Yeah.
Um
So, we are looking at setting up
something for New York, something for
Newark, something for Philly.
Philly right now won't be a book talk,
it'll just be a book signing.
Um
I haven't talked to Jeannie in a while,
but I'm cool with Jeannie.
Um
What happened with Tamagomari? Tamari
ain't shit.
What did Tamari Mari say?
Rolando said, "Ooh."
At Word Up bookstore?
You know, to be quite honest, Celene,
the real tea is that I really need to
keep 100% of my book sales at present.
So, you know, there's a future where I
go to bookstores and I split the
profits, but at the present time, I need
to get
my 100%.
And so, bookstores traditionally will
split the they'll split your sales with
you. And so, you know, I'm I'm not
really trying to like
um
I'm basically linking up with bookstores
that either are down and see the value
in having me in their space with that or
um they're just like,
"We get it."
Oh, yeah, lol gag lol gag
lol gagum. Yes, I saw that. And I
absolutely after I saw
her post that, I sent her
um
a post this white girl mocking them
being like,
"Okay, if you
don't
If you have a problem with cheering
people on
or
bad people, you're a bad person."
I don't know the date um for Philly yet.
I'll know it soon.
Exactly. I'm not Listen, the swirl
shouldn't have shit to do
with the values you exist in.
I used to be really against the swirl,
but now I'm just like as long as it
lines up with your values, I'm here for
whatever.
I'm here for whatever.
Damn, I was almost done.
But I didn't quite get there.
I didn't quite get
there. I didn't quite get there. I
didn't quite get there.
I didn't quite finish doing the pins.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Uh uh uh
I'm delirious.
I should go to sleep.
I got a book
on the road. What I totally forgot about
tour was how many goodies I come back
with.
Y'all, and when I tell you y'all be
giving gifts.
Listen, I've existed as a comic.
I've existed as
um
a host. I've been on the road in a
couple different forms.
But the best gifts have come from being
on the road as an intellectual and an
author.
Honey,
y'all be giving me some things.
We doing things.
So, here's a funny thing about Jedi.
When we downstairs, she act like she
don't know nobody.
When we downstairs, she don't really pay
me no mind.
But when I come up here,
it's just me and her and it's all this.
Look at all these snugs.
Yes, Reese.
I have lived many lives.
Hi, Lindsey.
Secret
lovers.
That's what we are. Trying so hard
to hide
the way we feel.
Useless what I put on there.
Skoo skoo da da da da.
Natasha.
Okay, lol gag him. No wonder I relate to
cats. We both have many lives.
Yeah.
Where the song breaks in the show,
Rishla?
Is Chicago?
You know I'm a stem.
I'm a stem, honey.
Terry D.
My
I
Chinese zodiac sign, I'm a cock.
And what would the ancestors say?
There's only one music break in What
Would the Ancestors Say?
Thank you, Rachel.
Kimberly, why am I in your Sims game?
No, Nadia, you do. It's just that
I didn't do it for the last 2 weeks cuz
I was on the road.
I don't do Halloween.
I don't do Halloween. For Halloween,
what I did was I lit a fire
and I sat by the fire
and I
um
I brought in I I like sent out the old
year.
Good night, Donna. Good night, Miss
Donna.
Oh my god, if we're